<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Huan Li's Personal Page</title>
    <description>Remember what should be remembered, and forget what should be forgotten. Alter what is changeable, and accept what is mutable. -- &lt;i&gt;The Catcher in the Rye&lt;/i&gt;
</description>
    <link>https://longaspire.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://longaspire.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 22:38:58 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 22:38:58 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A New Chapter in My Career</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/ZJU.png&quot; alt=&quot;Zhejiang University&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;Zhejiang University&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am thrilled to announce that I have recently taken a new step in my academic career by accepting the prestigious ZJU 100 Talent Program award from Zhejiang University, where I will be serving as a “Young Professor” and doctoral supervisor. This is a huge honor and I feel extremely grateful for the opportunity to contribute to the academic community at Zhejiang University and continue my growth as a researcher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before this new position, I had the privilege of serving as an assistant professor at Aalborg University from 2020 and a postdoctoral research fellow from 2019 to 2020. My time at Aalborg University was an incredibly enriching experience and I am thankful for the opportunities I had there to work with and learn from some of the most talented and dedicated professionals in my field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, I would like to express my gratitude to my colleagues and supervisors, especially Prof. Christian S. Jensen and Prof. Hua Lu, who have provided me with invaluable guidance and support throughout my time at Aalborg University. Their wisdom, expertise, and mentorship have helped me become a more mature researcher and I will carry their lessons with me for the rest of my career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, as I embark on this new chapter at Zhejiang University, I am filled with excitement and a sense of purpose. I am eager to work with my new colleagues and students, to continue my research, and to contribute to the growth and development of the university.
Additionally, I am overjoyed to have the opportunity to return to my old lab and reunite with familiar faces.
I believe that my experiences at Aalborg University and my passion for my field will serve me well in this new role, and I am eager to make the most of this incredible opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2023/02/post-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2023/02/post-1</guid>
        
        
        <category>personal information</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spatial Data Quality in the Internet of Things</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/MALOT.png&quot; alt=&quot;MALOT Project&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;MALOT Project&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the framework of our MALOT project, we have published two papers in prestigious venues.
Both papers are the outcomes of our literature review on spatial IoT data quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In November 2021, our long survey paper entitled &lt;strong&gt;Spatial Data Quality in the Internet of Things: Management, Exploitation, and Prospects&lt;/strong&gt; has been accepted by ACM Computing Surveys (IF: 10.3).
The abstract of this paper is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With the continued deployment of the Internet of Things (IoT), increasing volumes of devices are being deployed that emit massive spatially referenced data. Due in part to the dynamic, decentralized, and heterogeneous architecture of the IoT, the varying and often low quality of spatial IoT data (SID) presents challenges to applications built on top of this data. This survey aims to provide unique insight to practitioners who intend to develop IoT-enabled applications and to researchers who wish to conduct research that relates to data quality in the IoT setting. The survey offers an inventory analysis of major data quality dimensions in SID and covers significant data characteristics and associated quality considerations. The survey summarizes data quality related technologies from both task and technique perspectives. Organizing the technologies from the task perspective, it covers recent progress in SID quality management, encompassing location refinement, uncertainty elimination, outlier removal, fault correction, data integration, and data reduction; and it covers low-quality SID exploitation, encompassing querying, analysis, and decision-making techniques. Finally, the survey covers emerging trends and open issues concerning the quality of SID.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later in February 2022, our proposal submitted to SIGMOD 2022 tutorial track has been accepted.
The tutorial utilizes the structure of our survey paper and will be focusing on comparing the methodologies of representative works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope to release the full texts of both papers soon. Thank you to my knowledgeable mentors and collaborators, Prof. Christian S. Jensen from AAU, Prof. Hua Lu from RUC, Prof. Muhammad Aamir Cheema from Monash U, and Prof. Bo Tang from SUSTECH.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 22:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2022/02/post-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2022/02/post-1</guid>
        
        
        <category>publication</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Survey Paper about COVID-19 and IoT</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/MALOT.png&quot; alt=&quot;MALOT Project&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;MALOT Project&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our survey paper &lt;strong&gt;Impact of COVID-19 on Adoption of IoT in Different Sectors&lt;/strong&gt; is now released at &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.07196&quot;&gt;arXiv&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abstract of this paper is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;COVID-19 has disrupted normal life and has enforced a substantial change in the policies, priorities and activities of individuals, organisations and governments. These changes are proving to be a catalyst for technology and innovation. In this paper, we discuss the pandemic’s impact on the adoption of the Internet of Things (IoT) in various broad sectors namely healthcare, smart homes, smart buildings, smart cities, transportation and industrial IoT. Our analysis of this impact on IoT adoption is based on interviews with many industry experts, a thorough research literature review and a careful examination of reports from leading consulting firms. For each of these sectors, we also provide the details of recent initiatives taken in the wake of COVID-19. We also highlight challenges that need to be addressed and important research directions that will facilitate accelerated IoT adoption in these sectors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This survey contains the most recent research papers about how IoT is incorporated into and affected by COVID-19 in vertical sectors such as healthcare, smart homes, smart buildings, smart cities, transportation, and industrial IoT.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2021/01/post-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2021/01/post-1</guid>
        
        
        <category>publication</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Information of DBU Course (Fall 2020)</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;last-semester&quot;&gt;Last Semester&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Textbook: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Head First SQL&lt;/code&gt; (Lynn Beighley)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Content:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduction (today) + basic SQL statements&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SELECT, DELETE, UPDATE, NULL values&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be normal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ALTER, advanced UPDATE and SELECT&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multiple tables, creating table from data, Cartesion joins&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Joins and subqueries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More joins and set operators&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ER modeling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Constraints, views, transactions, and security&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Database applications (1)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Database applications (2), review, and information about the exam&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arrangement (except the first):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Exercises for the first half&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lectures for the second half&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Exercises/lectures the same venue!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning Goal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Professional terminology of the subject of database
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Proper understanding and use of relevant terms&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grasp of SQL statements
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Use the right constructs and correct formulation (syntax) to solve practical problems.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CRUD: Create/Read/Update/Delete data.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be able to know/do good database design
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;What, how and why?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Database applications
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Application development and tuning&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Database administration (a little)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;How to share your data conveniently and safely?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exam:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open book, written exam&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Question types
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Multiple choices&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Matching&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;SQL writing&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;ERD designing and table creating&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 05:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-2</guid>
        
        
        <category>teaching</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Teaching DBU Course (Fall 2020)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I will be a lecturer of AAU’s BAIT3 course &lt;strong&gt;Database Development (DBU)&lt;/strong&gt;. Danile Dell’Anglio will coordinate this course with me. The course consists of a series of lectures, larger exercises, and student presentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will announce more details soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-1</guid>
        
        
        <category>teaching</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ISQEA Project Open-sourced</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/IndoorLBS.png&quot; alt=&quot;Indoor-LBS Project&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;Indoor-LBS Project&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a part of Prof. Hua Lu’s DFF project &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://indoorlbs.github.io/&quot;&gt;DATA MANAGEMENT FOUNDATIONS FOR INDOOR LBS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, the open-sourced project ISQEA (‘Experimental Analysis of Indoor Spatial Queries’) is released at Github &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/indoorLBS/ISQEA&quot;&gt;https://github.com/indoorLBS/ISQEA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. This project contains an in-depth benchmark with datasets, evaluation tasks, and performance metrics. The datasets consist of real and synthetic data characterized by distinctive indoor topology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with this project, an experimental paper entitled ‘‘An Experimental Analysis of Indoor Spatial Queries: Modeling, Indexing, and Processing’’ has been submitted to IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering. This paper refers to an extensive experimental evaluation of five indoor space model/indexes that support four typical indoor spatial queries, namely range query (RQ), k nearest neighbor query (kNNQ), shortest path query (SPQ), and shortest distance query (SDQ). Our evaluation concerns the costs in model/index construction and query processing using a model/index.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tiantian Liu is the main contributor of this project and I am an important participant. We will continue to maintain this project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 02:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-4</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-4</guid>
        
        
        <category>research</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Indoor-LBS Project Site Online Now</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/IndoorLBS.png&quot; alt=&quot;Indoor-LBS Project&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;Indoor-LBS Project&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The website of Prof. Hua Lu’s DFF project &lt;strong&gt;DATA MANAGEMENT FOUNDATIONS FOR INDOOR LBS&lt;/strong&gt; is currently online. You can find it at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://indoorlbs.github.io/&quot;&gt;https://indoorlbs.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is supported by Independent Research Fund Denmark (Grant No. 8022-00366B). Its hosts include Roskilde University and Aalborg University. I was a member of this project and will still work as a close collaborator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will continue to publish any news and results in this venue.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-3</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/07/post-3</guid>
        
        
        <category>funding</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MSCA Project Site Online Now</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/MALOT.png&quot; alt=&quot;MALOT Project&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;MALOT Project&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy to let you know that a website of our EU MSCA project &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cordis.europa.eu/project/id/882232&quot;&gt;MALOT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is released now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find it at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://msca-malot.github.io/&quot;&gt;https://msca-malot.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. We will continue to publish any news and results in this venue.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/06/post-2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/06/post-2</guid>
        
        
        <category>funding</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Assistant Professorship at AAU</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a period of seeking faculty positions at universities, I decided to accept the Assistant Professor offer from Aalborg University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I have been working at AAU for a while and have developed a strong attachment to it. In addition, the offer from AAU provides a good integration with my MSCA fellowship such that I can still work on my fellowship while participating in the teaching activities as a faculty member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this period, I also participated in interviews with other institutions and met many excellent researchers. Although I did not choose to join them, I hope we will have cross in our future path, such as academic collaborations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working as an AP means that I will undertake more teaching tasks. As a green hand, I will strive to improve my lecturing skills and complete pedagogy training programs with passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will probably start my professorship from July or August this year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/06/post-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/06/post-1</guid>
        
        
        <category>personal information</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get to MSCA Implementation</title>
        <description>&lt;dl class=&quot;wp-caption alignright&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px&quot;&gt;

&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/images/MALOT.png&quot; alt=&quot;MALOT Project&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;

&lt;dd&gt;MALOT Project&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am excited and looking forward to starting my MSCA project next week. I have read a documentation about how to implement the MSCA. I would like to share some useful information and also keep them as a memorandum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;open-access&quot;&gt;Open Access&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two parts about Open Access (OA), namely OA for publication and OA for data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For publication OA, all peer-reviewed publications in this project should be either green OA or golden OA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Green OA means the beneficiaries can deposit the final peer-reviewed manuscript in a repository of their choice. Some good repository for MSCA could be https://www.openaire.eu/.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Golden OA means the publication can be in open access journals, or in hybrid journals that both sell subscriptions and offer the option of making individual articles openly accessible.
Links to the repositories in question must be provided in the system (Project Continuous Reporting).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For research data OA, one must submit a Data Management Plan within 6 months of the start of the action and the obligation to deposit the research data in a research data repository (e.g, Zenodo).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;acknowledgement-of-eu-funding&quot;&gt;Acknowledgement of EU Funding&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This project has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No [number].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;career-development-plan&quot;&gt;Career Development Plan&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Plan should define the training requirements, taking into account the research objectives and subsequent career goals. No template is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deliverables-to-report&quot;&gt;Deliverables to Report&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are two types of deliverables which may have to be reported:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Management Plan: a document outlining how the research data will be handled during your project, and after it is completed. It describes what data will be collected / generated; what methodology and standards are used; whether and how this data will be shared and/or made open; and how it will be curated and preserved. The DMP must be submitted within the first 6 months of the project. A DMP template is available at&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ethics requirements (if there were ethical issues)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unit-costs&quot;&gt;Unit Costs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two parts, namely Researcher Costs and Institutional Costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For researcher costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Living Allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobility Allowance. It is intended to cover the costs associated with the fact that you have moved to a different country in order to take up your position. This sum will not be audited and is flexible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Family Allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For institutional costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research, Training and Network Costs. This amount is intended to cover the costs associated with your project as
outlined in grant agreement, for example attending training courses, conferences, or when going on secondment. This should also  cover the cost of research (e.g. consumables), as appropriate, and can also be used to cover other related costs, such as visas.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Management and Indirect Costs. This is for university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;submission-of-reports&quot;&gt;Submission of Reports&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the report, you will be required to report on the scientific progress of your project, as well as your training and transfer of knowledge activities, secondments (if any), career development, the scientific management of the project, dissemination and communication activities, and on the project’s overall impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your report must be submitted within 60 days following the end date of the project. Submission of this report is a precondition for payment of the remaining amounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;submission-of-questionnaires&quot;&gt;Submission of Questionnaires&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funded researchers are requested to submit two questionnaires about their experience: one immediately following the completion of the project (“Evaluation Questionnaire”) and one two years later (“Follow-up Questionnaire”)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-marie-curie-alumni-association&quot;&gt;The Marie Curie Alumni Association&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Established as a not-for-profit organization in 2014, the Association offers opportunities for networking and peer exchange, an alumni directory, job offers, an events calendar, and other services of potential interest to IF researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/04/post-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://longaspire.github.io/post/2020/04/post-1</guid>
        
        
        <category>funding</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
